{
    "id": "8f8421ddaa7c43b3b3586f2e48b9f824",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………… people believe in ghosts.",
            "description": "Before a noun without a determiner, we use most.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Has she got ………………………………. friends?",
            "description": "In questions we use any some is mainly used in affirmative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "any of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. key opens the door.",
            "description": "Before a noun without a determiner we use neither.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… these answers is correct.",
            "description": "We use neither of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… my friends wished me on my birthday.",
            "description": "None of means not a single one of.",
            "answers": [
                "No of",
                "None",
                "None of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t watched …………………………….. his movies.",
            "description": "We use any of before a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "any of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………. turned up for my party.",
            "description": "No one means the same as nobody.",
            "answers": [
                "Nobody",
                "No one",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t take it ………………………………. longer.",
            "description": "No longer is similar to not any longer.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "no",
                "not any"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t live here ………………………….  more.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "no",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………. his ideas are complicated.",
            "description": "We use all of before a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I ask ………………………………. questions?",
            "description": "Use 'a few' to mean 'a small number of'.",
            "answers": [
                "a few",
                "the few",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I earn ……………………………. than I used to.",
            "description": "Less can be used as an adverb. It is the opposite of more. ",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}